Privacy Policy
--------------

iSideWith is an interactive platform that matches your political beliefs with candidates, issues and ballot measures and gives you the tools to share, compare and discuss your beliefs with other people.

Our goal is to provide you with useful information so you can make an educated decision at the ballot box.

Protecting your personal information is very important to us and we have tried to keep this Privacy Policy as simple as possible to explain what information we collect and what we do with that information.

If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy please use the “contact us” link at the bottom of this page.

We collect information from our users in order to provide you with a personalized, useful and efficient experience. The categories of information we collect can include:

**Personal Data**

When you log in to iSideWith through various social media, including Facebook, Twitter, Google, Yahoo or other sites, we may receive information from the social network including your profile information, profile picture, gender, user name, user ID associated with your social media account, age range, language, country, friends list, and any other information you permit the social network to share with third parties. We will never share any of this data with third parties. The data we receive is dependent upon your privacy settings with the social network, and we will never post information about you on third party social media sites without your consent. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to our website or Service.

Personal Data does not include aggregate information, which is data we collect about the use of our Site or about a group or category of services or users, from which individual identities, contact information, or other personal information has been removed.

**Anonymous Data**

Anonymous Data means data that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Data; Anonymous Data does not, by itself, permit the identification of individual persons. This includes answers to our political quiz or polls, or aggregate information which is data we collect about the use of our Site or about a group or category of services or users, from which individual identities or other personal information has been removed.

When you use iSideWith, some data is automatically collected, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring website, and your activity on our Site. We never treat this information as Personal Information and only use it as an aggregate without personal identifiers.

We may also automatically collect certain information through the use of cookies or web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive at the request of a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Site and your experience. For example, we use cookies to identify you so that, for example, when you return to our site, if you've already completed the questionnaire, you don't have to repeat it in order to access your personalized voting guide. If we link cookies to any personally identifying information, we will treat this information as Personal Information. If you wish to block, erase, or be warned of cookies, please refer to your browser manufacturer to learn about these functions. However, if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect certain features on our Site. Web beacons are small, invisible graphic images that may be used on iSideWith or in emails relating to iSideWith to monitor traffic on our Site and to understand how people are using our Site and our various products and services when they are offered on third party sites.

The Site may contain links to other web sites. iSideWith is not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Policy applies solely to information collected by our Site.

**What We Do With Your Information**

We use your Personal Information to give you relevant information. For example, we use your quiz responses to match you to political candidates and parties. If you sign and save your results we may use your email address to send you a link to your voting guide, a reminder to vote or information about political issues, candidates and elections.

We do not sell, rent or otherwise share your Personal Information with any third parties except in the following limited circumstances:

• Compliance with Law. We may preserve or disclose your Personal Information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation, or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security, or technical issues; or to protect iSideWith’s rights or property.

• Business Transfers. The promises in this Policy will apply to your Personal Information in the event that iSideWith is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization, or a sale of assets. However, your information may be transferred to another entity as part of that transaction.

**Sharing Your Information**

If you create an account with us to save your quiz results your Personal Information will be kept private. If you choose to join a discussion your username will be visible to other users but your other Personal Information, such as your email address, will be kept private unless you choose to share that information in your Privacy Settings.

Sharing is a two-way street meant to benefit all users. Please remember that if you choose to make your profile and quiz results public to other users your profile information, including your name and photo, and your actions on the Service, will be available publicly to other users on the Service and some of this information may be searchable by search engines.

**Advertising**

You may notice an advertisement on our site from a candidate, party or political organization. We may work with ad networks and other third parties to serve you online advertisements. This helps us provide our service for free to our users and inform you about organizations that share your passion on specific issues. We may share information with advertisers in an aggregated and anonymous form that does not reasonably identify you directly as an individual. We do not share your personal information, political quiz answers, or voting preferences with our advertisers unless you explicitly agree to share that information or be contacted by them.

We may allow third party online advertising networks to collect information about your use of our website over time so that they may display ads that may be relevant to your interests on our Service as well as on other websites or apps.

**Changing Your Personal Information**

If you log in to save your results or participate in a discussion and would like to modify or delete your information please notify us using the “contact us” link at the bottom of this page.

**Security**

Please be responsible and protect your account with a strong password. If you notice any suspicious activity in your account, please email us immediately using the “contact us” link at the bottom of this page.

**Minors**

iSideWith does not intentionally gather Personal Data from visitors who are under the age of 13. If a child under the age of 13 submits Personal Data to us and we learn that the Personal Data is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible. If you believe that we might have any Personal Data from a child under the age of 13, please inform us using the “contact us” link at the bottom of this page.

**International Users**

If you live outside the United States and provide us with data, you agree that your Personal Data may be processed for the purposes identified in the Privacy Policy. In addition, your Personal Data may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding processing of Personal Data may be less stringent than the laws in your country. By providing your data, you consent to such transfer.

**Feedback**

We value your opinions to make our site more useful and relevant. Please email us using the “contact us” link at the bottom of this page.

**Enforcement**

iSideWith is based in the United States and the privacy laws of the United States govern the use of our Site.

**Changes To This Policy**

We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy at any time. We will make clear that changes have been made by indicating on the Policy the date it was last updated. Unless otherwise stated in the amendment, the amended Policy will automatically be effective seven days after it is initially posted on the Site. We encourage you to review this Policy from time to time to make sure that you understand how any Personal Information you provide will be used.

Questions or comments regarding your privacy or this Policy should be sent using the “contact us” link at the bottom of this page.

Effective date of this version: Feb 15, 2020.

[About](https://www.isidewith.com/about/)  •   [Polls](https://www.isidewith.com/polls)  •   [Donate](https://isidewithdonate.com/)  •   [FAQs](https://www.isidewith.com/faqs/)  •     •   [Candidate Login](https://www.isidewith.com/candidate-login/)  •  [Data & Insights](https://www.isidewith.com/insights/)  •   [Privacy](https://www.isidewith.com/privacy-policy/)  •   [Terms](https://www.isidewith.com/terms-of-use/)

iSideWith is not affiliated with any political party, candidate, or interest group.
